Guide to the Gustav Henry Bliesner Papers 1934-1985
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Gustav Henry Bliesner Papers
1934-1985
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Cage 220
Bliesner, Gustav Henry, 1910-1994.
51.5 Linear feet of shelf space 103 boxes
Gustav Bliesner (1910-1994) was an electrical engineer and an expert on rural electrification, sprinkler systems, and hydroelectric dams. He consulted on industrial and military projects, and on electrical systems for the United States space program. The collection is comprised of Gustav Bliesner's scrapbooks, journals, correspondence, professional documents, office files, along with a large quantity of miscellaneous collected material, primarily printed ephemera.
Gustav Bliesner (1910-1994) was an electrical engineer and an expert on rural electrification, sprinkler systems, and hydroelectric dams. He consulted on industrial and military projects, and on electrical systems for the United States space program.
Bliesner was born at Fairfield, Washington; he graduated from Rockford High School and attended Washington State College, where he earned his bachelor's degree in electrical engineering in 1933. In the following year he finished his Master of Science degree. In 1939 he received his professional engineering degree, and later became a Ph.D. candidate at Iowa State College. During his career as an engineer he taught at local universities, worked with the Army Corps of Engineers, Boeing, North American Aviation, and the Bonneville Power Administration. Mr. Bliesner was an expert in the field of rural electrification whose long and distinguished career included participation in projects such as the Grand Coulee Dam and the Boeing KC-135.
The collection is comprised of Gustav Bliesner's scrapbooks, journals, correspondence, professional documents, office files, along with a large quantity of miscellaneous collected material, primarily printed ephemera. Bliesner carefully and painstakingly documented his professional activities and accomplishments; his civic and social activities are also represented. The scrapbook volumes, which Bliesner called "My Life's Philosophy," constitute the bulk of the collection.
The collection has been arranged in four series. The first and largest series is made up of scrapbooks that Bliesner titled "My Life's Philosophy." These scrapbooks are maintained in the order that Mr. Bliesner created them and follow a generally chronological sequence. Bliesner assigned volume numbers and titles to each scrapbook. The second series is a separate sequence of scrapbook volumes. These were accessioned at later dates but are also part of Bliesner's "My Life's Philosophy." The third series is Bliesner's office files, arranged in Bliesner's original decimal system. An index to these files is located in box 79. Series four is arranged by subject, and is sometimes only roughly sorted.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Gustav Bliesner donated these papers in multiple installments, circa 1967-1985.
In addition to the collection described in this guide, the WSU Libraries hold several unprocessed accessions of Gustav Bliesner's papers: MS 1982-37, MS 1983-19, MS 1984-40, MS 1985-22, MS 1986-18, MS 1989-36, MS 1991-20, MS 1994-39.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Bliesner, Gustav Henry, 1910-1994 -- Archives
Grand Coulee Dam (Wash.)
Hydroelectric power plants.; Rural electrification.; Electrical engineers -- Archives.
Public Utilities; Public Works; Washington (State)
- Series 1: "My Life's Philosophy" volumes, first sequence, 1934-1967
  - Farm Electrification volume 2, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Volume 1, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Volume 2, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Volume 3, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Volume 4, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Volume 5, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Volume 6, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Volume 7, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Volume 8, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Volume 9, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Volume 10, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Volume 11, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Volume 12, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Volume 13, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Volume 14, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Volume 15, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Administration, Education, and Research (War, Power, and Agriculture) 1, volume 17, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Administration, Education, and Research (The Family and Its Problems) 2, volume 18, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Administration, Education, and Research (Industrial Relations Engineering) 3-1, volume 19, 1943 (Three volumes of "The Victory Fleet" detailing shipbuilding during World War II, information on industries with United States military contracts, War Producti (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Administration, Education, and Research (Industrial Relations Engineering) 3-2, volume 20, 1943 (Newspaper clippings and information on shipbuilding) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Administration, Education, and Research (Industrial Relations Engineering) 3-3, volume 21, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Administration, Education, and Research (early preliminary Doctoral studies) 4, volume 22, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Commission Pending and Doctor of Philosophy 1 and 2, volume 23, 1943-1944 (Army Specialized Training Program, ASTP, and Navy College Program,V-12, at Iowa State College during World War II) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Doctor of Philosophy 2, 3 and 4, volume 24, 1943-1944 (Ph.D. work at Iowa State College) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Naval Training School 1, volume 25, 1944 (Naval electrical engineering training at Iowa State College during World War II) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Application in Public Administration, volume 26, 1944 (education and employment history to 1944) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Abstract of in-service fellowship in public administration, volume 27, 1944-1945 (Official correspondence regarding Bliesner's education, work experiences, and service record) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, volume 28, 1944-1945 (Agricultural engineering, food production, electrical engineering, soil and water conservation, compiled in book format for WSC Extension Service, 1944 November-1945 October 31) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, volume 29, 1945-1946 (Agricultural engineering, food production, electrical engineering, soil and water conservation, compiled in book format for WSC Extension Service, 1945 November 1-1946 December 1) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Institutions of Advanced Education, volume 31, 1946 (Correspondence regarding employment and education at various institutions of higher learning, 1942 December 10-1947 March 8) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Gustav Henry Bliesner, Ph.D., volume 32-41 (bound together), 1946 (State of Washington engineering examinations, Iowa State personnel forms) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Farragut College, volume 42, 1947 (Information regarding the establishment of Farragut College at the former site of Farragut Naval Training Station in Idaho) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Farragut College of Engineering, volume 43, 1947 (Details of Bliesner's involvement with Farragut College, Lutheran Churches, Alpha Kappa Lambda at WSU, YMCA, U.S. Navy, and Engineering) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - School of Mines and Metallurgy, volume 44, 1947 (Bliesner's role in Alpha Kappa Lambda postwar expansion, and developing a department of engineering at Farragut College) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Work on my Ph.D., volume 45, 1948 (personal history, church affiliations, fraternal organizations, government service, and educational experience) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Developing an Engineering College, volume 46, 1947-1948 (Correspondence, WSU football programs, United States Marine Corps Reserve leaflets) (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - Academic Accreditation, volume 47, 1948 (Farragut College and Technical Institute course listings, grade sheets, course requirements) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Public Power, volume 48, 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
  - Public Power, volume 49, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Chronological personal, volume 52, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - A Job in 1951, volume 51, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Preliminary Cost Report on the Construction of the Parker-Pilot Knob 161-kv Transmission Line, volume 52, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Cost Data Subject Matter, volume 53, 1951 (Addendum report for the construction of the Parker-Pilot Knob 161-kv Transmission Line) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Blythe Substation, volume 55, 1951 (Reports, work summaries, schematic drawings, diagrams, and information on the construction of the Blythe substation) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Zion Lutheran Church, volume 56, 1949-1951 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Gila Substation, volume 57, 1949-1951 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Colorado River Indian Reservation, volume 58, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Another Connection, volume 59, 1951-1952 (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
  - The Deep South, volume 60, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Personnel Management, volume 61, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - This is the Life, volume 62, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Back to School, volume 63, 1952-1953 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
  - Lutheran Church of the Reformation, volume 64, 1952-1953 (Church writings and papers from the Lutheran Church of the Reformation in Savannah, GA) (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
  - Clark Hill Power and Transmission System, volume 65, 1952-1953 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hydrogen Age, volume 66, 1952-1953 (Newspaper clippings from Eisenhower-Stevenson presidential race, applications to the U.S. Civil Service, university organization pamphlets, news article commemorating the tenth anniversary of Pearl Harbor) (Box 21, Folder 2-4)
  - Original Ph.D. Writings, volume 67, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 5-7)
  - Training the Professional Engineer, volume 68, 1948-1953 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
  - Appendix, Transmission, and Rural Electrical Distribution Loop Services, volume 69, 1946-1956 (Papers from Clark Hill Project, Transmission Line at Hunter Air Force Base, Blythe Substation, Davis Dam, Boulder Dam Transmission Line, and Senate Bill for the (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Pertinent Positions, volume 71, 1943-1958 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Hope Lutheran Church (Portland, OR), volume 72, 1952-1954 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - The Dalles Project, volume 73, 1943-1958 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
  - Engineering, volume 74, 1944-1953 (Report on Washington irrigation, 1946 April; Irrigation pamphlets; Engineer society bulletins; Bliesner's Civil Service ratings; Report for Washington State College extension services: "Wiring the Farm") (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
  - University of Portland, volume 75, 1953-1954 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Portland Public Schools, volume 76, 1954 (Pay charts, attendance records, course outlines, adult vocational education and apprentice programs) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1954-55-80 Program, volume 77, 1954 (Work orders, Federal Power Commission utilities usage report, electrical engineering diagrams, correspondence, report on river and harbor projects: Dalles Dam, Columbia River, Willamette River, and Umpqua River) (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Experiments Lectures and Problems, volume 78, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Project History MA-2 Wiring System, volume 79, 1955 (Report for Boeing Airplane Co., 1955 June 30) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbooks, volume 80, 1952-1954 (Football and baseball programs, vocational education information, Portland School of Engineering Papers, California science and engineering recruitment circular, 1952 July, newspaper clippings) (Box 26, Folder 1-6)
  - Energy Conversion, volume 81A, 1952-1955 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Energy Conversion, volume 81B, 1951-1955 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Energy Conversion 1952-55 volume 81C, 1952-1955 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - St. Mathews Lutheran Church (Renton, Washington), volume 82, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Ph.D. Thesis Addenda, volume 83, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - KC 135 Electrical System Diagrams, volume 84, 1956 January 9-1954 August 25 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Formal-Informal Test Results, volume 85, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of S.P.E.E.A Executive Committee Meetings, volume 86, 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Contract S.P.E.E.A., W.E.A., B.A.C., volume 87, 1956-1957 (negotiations with Boeing, letters, questionnaires, newspaper clippings) (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Guided Missiles, volume 88A, 1956-1958 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Guided Missiles, volume 88B, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Individual Income Tax Reports, volume 89, 1955-1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Sample Publications, volume 90A, 1934-1965 (pipeline corrosion in the sub-Arctic, corrosion survey Haines-Fairbanks P.O.L. pipeline, specifications for magnesium anodes-cathodic protection) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Sample Publications, volume 90B, 1934-1965 (Oregon State College information packet for new faculty, 1948; "Country Electrification" by Bliesner; University of Portland syllabi and laboratory schedules) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Sample Publications, volume 90C, 1934-1965 (Box 31, Folder 2-4)
  - The Electrical System, volume 91, 1956-1957 (Schematics, generator outlines, wiring diagrams, D.C. motor and generator design) (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Feasibility Study of the D.C. system LVTP 5 Diesel Drive, volume 92, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Samples of My Life's Work, volume 93, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1957 (newspaper clippings, church circulars, correspondence, automobile advertisements) (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
  - Electrical Engineering, volume 94A, 1957 (electrical distribution and street lighting, Corps of Engineers construction guide, U.S.E.D. Portland Division Power Definitions) (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Electrical Engineering, volume 94B, 1957 (electrical distribution specifications, barracks blueprints and project notes, Ft. Richardson, Alaska) (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Electrical Engineering, volume 94C, 1958 (daily log, 1958; "How magnetic and capacity fields affect the relationship in alternating current circuits"; Chapel with educational wing, Ladd Air Force Base; engineering magazines and pamphlets) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Engineering, volume 94D, 1958 (1958 desk calendar, Alaska Corps of Engineers papers from 1958, electrical equipment brochures, radar tower modifications for Tatalina Air Force station Alaska, Army housing procedure manual, design analysis and p (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Electrical Engineering, volume 94E, 1958 (newspaper clippings on Alaska statehood and engineering, engineering magazines) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Electrical Engineering, volume 94F, 1958-1959 (Rural Electrification Administration bulletins and engineering magazines, professional notes, electrical engineer state exams, Swedish State Power Board publications, 1950) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Engineering, volume 94G, 1959 (Newspaper clippings, professional notes, specifications for water supply system at Granite Mountain Air Force station Alaska, Corps of Engineers project notes for Alaska, notebook) (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Lakeridge Lutheran Church (Seattle), volume 95A, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report 1960 (Lakeridge Lutheran Church), volume 95B (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
  - Alpha Kappa Lambda 1957-59 volume 96A, 1957-1959 (newsletters, construction news for new chapter house in Pullman, WSU and national chapter information) (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
  - Alpha Kappa Lambda 1957-59 volume 96A (continued) (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Alpha Kappa Lambda Fraternity Advisors Association, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - The Present Situation, volume 97, 1957-1958 (university tuition rates at Pacific Lutheran College and Washington State College, personal correspondence, cathodic protection study notes 7-8-57, Ft. Richardson Alaska electric distribution map, electronic an (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Seattle University, volume 98, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Generator, volume 99, 1957 (calculations from Boeing Airplane Company, wire and circuit breaker guide for electrical design Boeing, Kato generator blueprint, altitude simulation chamber packet from Murphy and Miller Inc, Detroit Diesel brochures, v (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Elements of Electrical Engineering, volume 100, 1957-1958 (sample lectures, grade sheets, class schedules, experiment and lecture notes on fundamentals of electrical engineering) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Wilderness Acre, volume 101A, 1958 (gardening journals, press book of plants from Alaskan sub-Arctic, 1957) (Box 37, Folder 2-4)
  - Estimating, volume 102, 1957-1958 (Engineer Corps manual on engineering and design cost estimates March 1959, EM 1110-345-730, Northwest Airlines system route map, electrical distribution notes, U.S. Army housing bids and price schedule) (Box 37, Folder 5-6)
  - Estimating, volume 102, 1957-1958 (continued) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Direct Current Class notes, Experiment, volume 103, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Alternating Current Class notes and Experiments, volume 104, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook 1956 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Volume 106A, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
  - Volume 106B, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
  - Volume 106C, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
  - Volume 106D, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
  - Volume 106E, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
  - Volume 106F, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 6-7)
  - Volume 106G, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
  - Volume 106H, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Volume 106I, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Volume 106J, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Volume 106K, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Volume 106L, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Volume 106M, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 5-6)
  - Volume 106N, 1959-1960 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Volume 106O, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Volume 106P, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Electrical Distribution Standards, volume 107, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
  - Volume 108A, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
  - Volume 108B, 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 3-4)
  - Volume 108C, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Engineering Manuals, volume 109, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 6-7)
  - Shop Drawings and Guide Specifications, volume 110, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - Contract D.A. Invitation, volume 111, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum Vitae, volume 112, 1910 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Abstract of Education and Experience, volume 112B, circa 1960 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Addendum Data to Accompany Curriculum Vitae, volume 112C, circa 1960 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, circa 1950-1959 (Box 46, Folder 3-5)
  - Electrical, volume 113, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
  - Annual Proceedings of Education Program, volume 114A, 1959-1962 (Box 47, Folder 1-3)
  - Annual Proceedings of Education Program 1959-62 114B, 1959-1962 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Supervisors Training, volume 116, 1959-1961 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Seventy-fifth AIEE Convention, volume 117, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Electrical and Electronic, volume 118, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 2-3)
  - Electrical and Electronic Education with Professional Practice, volume 119, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Bliesner Engineering Services, volume 120A, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Bliesner Engineering Services, volume 120B, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
  - Office Notebook, volume 121, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Current Projects, volume 122, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 5-6)
  - Recent Samples of My Work, volume 123, 1959-1963 (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
  - The Boy Scouts, volume 128, 1935-1965 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
  - The Bliesner House, volume 129, 1959-1961 (Box 51, Folder 3-4)
  - The Boeing Company, volume 130, 1954-1962 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - NATMC and NASA Conferences at Seattle World's Fair, volume 132, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 6-7)
  - Notebooks, volume 133, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 1-5)
  - Getting a Job, volume 134, 1962 (Box 52, Folder 6-7)
  - Current Chronological, volume 135, 1961-1965 (Box 52, Folder 8-10)
  - Current Chronological (continued) (Box 53, Folder 1-9)
  - IEEE Paper, volume 136, undated (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
  - Class notes and Newspaper clippings, volume 137A, 1963-1964 (Orange County State College notes and examinations) (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Electrical Engineering Exams, volume 138B, 1962-1963 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Brochure of Bliesner, volume 139A, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Brochure of Bliesner, volume 139B, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 3-4)
  - Brochure of Bliesner, volume 139C, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Volume 139D, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Professional Record and Resume, volume 140, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - North American Aviation, volume 142, 1963-1965 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Emanuel Lutheran Church (La Habra, CA), volume 143, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 3-4)
  - La Habra Fellowship of Churches, volume 144, 1961-1965 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Rural Electrification Transmission-Distribution Loop and Network Services, Bliesner Ph.D. Thesis, volume 145A, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - UNESCO File, volume 146A, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Supervisory Electric Utilities Engineer with Office Copy, volume 146B, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
  - Job Applications, volume 146C, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Job Applications, volume 146D, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
  - Job Applications, volume 146E, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Acting Chairman Department of Electrical Engineering, volume 147, 1964 (Northridge College of Science and Engineering) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Manpower Utilization Charts, Letters, Procedure, volume 148, 1964-1966 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
  - Special Power Distribution Project for Saturn S-II, Seal Beach, CA, volume 149, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Continued Education, volume 150, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Design and Estimates, volume 151, 1961-1964 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Another Position, volume 153A, 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Academic, volume 153B, 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Brochure of Bliesner, volume 153B2, 1966-1967 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Personal File, volume 154, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - IEEE Fellow Grade, volume 156, 1965-1967 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Current Chronological (TDY New York), volume 157, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 4-5)
  - Welcome to Vietnam, Thailand (PCS 168th Engineer Combat Battalion), volume 158, 1965-1967 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Left Over Job Exhibits, Resumes etc., volume 159, 1964-1967 (includes Vietnam casualty report list, U.S. Army Engineer Command Vietnam) (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Air Force Regional Civil Engineers (ASEE Convention WSU 1966), volume 160, 1965-1967 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Office Notebook, volume 161, 1965-1967 (Box 61, Folder 3-4)
  - Home Notebook, volume 162, 1965-1967 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - "Back Home" Recommendation Letters, volume 163, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Office Notebook, volume 164, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Folder 1961-65, volume 165, 1961-1965 (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
  - Gardening Notebook, volume 166, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Office Folder 1962-63, volume 167, 1962-1963 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Folder 1962-63, volume 168, 1962-1963 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Lighting and Power Wakefield Facility Santa Anna, volume 169, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 7-8)
  - Organization 1963-64, volume 170, 1963-1964 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Utility Planning and Design, volume 171, 1964-1965 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Lecture Notes, volume 172A, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Lecture Notes and newspaper clippings, volume 172B, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Heating and Power Survey Elmendorf-Fort Richardson Area, volume 173, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Brochure: Carl K. Barstow, Consulting Mechanical Engineer, volume 174, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Slauson Modifications Project Notebook, volume 175, 1963-1964 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Modification of the Slauson Facility, volume 176, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Instructions to Bidder for Installation of Data Acquisition System at Propulsion Systems Development Facility, Las Cruces, NM; North American Aviation Inc., volume 177, undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Brochure: Technical-Engineer-Architect Management, volume 178, undated (Box 63, Folder 10)